jukata.com 2011-11-25

# Jukata™ - Your Life, Your Music

_Effective Date of Current Policy: July 1st, 2009_

Jukata ("Jukata," "we," "us") shares your concerns about the protection of your personal information online. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes our practices regarding the collection and use of information through our website and the JuK mobile client on your handset (collectively, the “ Service”. By using the Service or obtaining any product using the Service. you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this Policy. _If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site_.

We may from time to time update this Policy. We will notify you of changes to the Policy by posting the updated Policy on this page. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of the Policy.

**What kind of information do we collect?**

We collect a variety of information for various purposes. We collect personal information, such as your name and email address during your registration for Jukata “Service” If you download software, your name and email information will be required. In addition, to use any aspect of the Service, you may be required to register and provide certain information including a member or user name, a password, a valid email address (together the “Account Information”) or a credit card. We do not collect personal information from children we know to be under the age of 13. We also collect demographic information in a number of other ways. We keep track of the domains from which people visit our Website. For legal and business reasons, we may track the country or zip code of the visitor. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and for federal export law compliance, when required. This information is analyzed at an aggregate level. Finally, we collect statistical browser information on the anonymous users of our Website, including: (1) the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the user's computer, (2) the referring URL, if any, and/or (3) the browser software identification (this provides the brand and version of the browser software used by the anonymous user while viewing our Website). This is not personally identifiable information.

**How does Jukata collect information?**

We collect information in several ways. For example, we use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement through the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses do not provide us with personally identifiable information such as your name, physical address, email address or telephone number. Cookies are pieces of data that are stored on your hard drive which contains personal information. We use cookies to identify your installation of Slacker software, as well as to identify the version of the software you are currently using. Cookies may also be used to auto-sign you into your account, as well as to store and authenticate your user name and password. Cookies are linked to your personal information so you may not have to sign in and enter a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site; however, you will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users in order to enhance their experience on our site. Rejecting cookies is done on your personal computer and through your browser settings. Finally, web pages may contain an electronic file called a web beacon, which allows a website to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. We research certain usage and activities on our website. Jukata uses web beacons to conduct this research, including on the Jukata website. The information collected through these web beacons is used to find out more about our users, for more accurate reporting, and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Information recorded through the use of these web beacons is aggregated. No personally identifiable information about you is shared by us with any person or entity as a result of this research.

**How do we use the information we collect?**

Following is a description of the different ways that Jukata uses the information we gather. Be aware, while we encourage all third parties involved in running our business to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and to otherwise handle personally identifiable information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from Jukata or independently.

**Non-personally identifiable information**

Jukata uses non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address and the pages that you visit on our Service, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website and improve -related services and features. Your IP address and other non-personally identifiable information also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the Site.

We also may share aggregated statistical data and other non-personally identifiable information with our current and potential business partners, and with our service providers.

**Personally identifiable information**

Jukata uses personally identifiable information collected from you to:  
provide support services;   
get in touch with you when necessary;  
contact you to make sure you are satisfied with our goods and services or to find out how we can serve you better;  
conduct in-depth marketing research regarding our customers and potential customers;   
verify access to access-restricted services such as our Forums and your mobile client;   
track content accesses and downloads for purposes of paying royalties and licenses to third party providers, for marketing purposes, and for enforcing our policies and procedures. 

You may, from time to time, receive information from us regarding new features, new products and services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you'd like to opt out of receiving future mailings from Jukata, please follow the procedure outlined in the Choice/Opt-out section below.

Jukata also may use your personally identifiable information to "pre-populate" forms that are used by the Site to facilitate transactions with us. Other types of use by us of personally identifiable information are discussed below.

**Online Surveys**

Jukata sometimes administers online surveys in connection with the Site in which we ask you for demographic information and opinions. We do not ask you for personally identifiable information as part of a survey. We use the collected survey data on an aggregated basis to better understand the needs of all of our customers.

**Certain Non-Marketing Uses**

Jukata may send to you periodic announcements regarding status updates, service changes concerning the Site and other administrative matters. Subject to applicable law, we reserve the right to release information concerning any Site visitor where such visitor is believed to be in violation of his or her obligations to us, is partaking (or is suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, in response to civil subpoenas and discovery requests, to protect the interests of Jukata, our customers or others, and as otherwise permitted or required by law.

**Third Party Websites**

Emails from Jukata or its or its business partners, and the Site itself, may contain links to other Internet websites, including sites that may or may not be owned or operated by Jukata. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites' use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when email recipients or Site visitors click through links to those sites. If you visit such websites, we encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of the sites.

**How your information is stored.**

Jukata seeks to use reasonable security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information that is under our control. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of the foregoing, while we seek to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and Jukata's servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Site. You provide all such information at your own risk.

**How To Update Your Personal Information**

If you have signed up for an account with Jukata you may update your mailing address, email address, name changes, Forum name, or billing information by accessing your account at www jukata.com policy where you can log into your account to review and update your personal information.

**Jukata Forums**

This Site may make chat rooms, forums and/or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Contacting Jukata**

If you have any questions about this Policy, the data collection and usage practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, or if you wish to report a violation of this Policy, please contact:
